[{"answer": "We're dead", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Virgin.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "We are dead", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "We are dead", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Virgin.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "All day tomorrow? We had a month and a half to come up with something and we didn't do anything", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "Hey, see those two women over there? I almost dated the one on the right. She's in the closet business", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Virgin.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "What is it your business", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "So, she mentioned she had a boyfriend and then it hit me. What do I need more closet space for?  Hi, my friend", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Virgin.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "my friend, my friend", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "my friend", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Virgin.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "my friend, my friend", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "What? I'm not married. I'm not allowed to go out with somebody else", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Virgin.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "Depends on what", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "Depends", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Virgin.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "On many factors", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "She got anything in your medicine cabinet", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Virgin.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "Ah hah. Let me ask you this. Is there any tampax in your house", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "This is your plan", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Virgin.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "I don't think you are", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "She's a virgin, she just told me", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Virgin.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "Well it's not like spotting a toupee", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "A virgin", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Virgin.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "I don't know. I'm very attracted to her. That accent, it's so sexy", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "I'm in. Let's go for it", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Virgin.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "I don't care, whatever", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "I don't care, whatever", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Virgin.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "Okay. What are you getting", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "I'll tell you what. Why don't we just get a couple of dishes and we'll just share 'em", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Virgin.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "I'm gonna get a Chow Fung", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "I'm gonna get a Chow Fung", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Virgin.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "It's a broad noodle", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "What's a Chow Fung", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Virgin.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "What do you mean, a broad noodle", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "What do you mean, a broad noodle", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Virgin.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "Well I don't want a big flat noodle", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "It's a big flat noodle", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Virgin.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "What kind of noodle do you want", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "Who says I want a noodle", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Virgin.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "All right. I'll get pea pods and you can't have any of my pea pods", "qsentId": 38}, {"answer": "So how are you guys comin' along", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Virgin.txt", "asentId": 41, "question": "Good.", "qsentId": 40}, {"answer": "Hello", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Virgin.txt", "asentId": 43, "question": "What's going on? What's going on? I'll tell you what's going on. I'm fired", "qsentId": 42}, {"answer": "What", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Virgin.txt", "asentId": 45, "question": "Another job", "qsentId": 44}]